[
    {
        "question": "Which country is Paris its capital?",
        "answer": "France"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is Washington, D.C. its capital?",
        "answer": "United States"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is London its capital?",
        "answer": "United Kingdom"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is Berlin its capital?",
        "answer": "Germany"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is Ottawa its capital?",
        "answer": "Canada"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is Rome its capital?",
        "answer": "Italy"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is Madrid its capital?",
        "answer": "Spain"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is Canberra its capital?",
        "answer": "Australia"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is Moscow its capital?",
        "answer": "Russia"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is Beijing its capital?",
        "answer": "China"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is Ankara its capital?",
        "answer": "Turkey"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is Seoul its capital?",
        "answer": "South Korea"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is Mexico City its capital?",
        "answer": "Mexico"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is Brasilia its capital?",
        "answer": "Brazil"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is New Delhi its capital?",
        "answer": "India"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is Buenos Aires its capital?",
        "answer": "Argentina"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is Pretoria its capital?",
        "answer": "South Africa"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is Tokyo its capital?",
        "answer": "Japan"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is Cairo its capital?",
        "answer": "Egypt"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is Riyadh its capital?",
        "answer": "Saudi Arabia"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is Bangkok its capital?",
        "answer": "Thailand"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is Amsterdam its capital?",
        "answer": "Netherlands"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is Warsaw its capital?",
        "answer": "Poland"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is Athens its capital?",
        "answer": "Greece"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is Lisbon its capital?",
        "answer": "Portugal"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is Oslo its capital?",
        "answer": "Norway"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is Helsinki its capital?",
        "answer": "Finland"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is Copenhagen its capital?",
        "answer": "Denmark"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is Stockholm its capital?",
        "answer": "Sweden"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is Vienna its capital?",
        "answer": "Austria"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is Baghdad its capital?",
        "answer": "Iraq"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is Abu Dhabi its capital?",
        "answer": "United Arab Emirates"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is Islamabad its capital?",
        "answer": "Pakistan"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is Caracas its capital?",
        "answer": "Venezuela"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is Santiago its capital?",
        "answer": "Chile"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is Lima its capital?",
        "answer": "Peru"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is Wellington its capital?",
        "answer": "New Zealand"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is Havana its capital?",
        "answer": "Cuba"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is Kigali its capital?",
        "answer": "Rwanda"
    }
]
